<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BrainTraining 2Go</string>
    <string name="app_description">Challenge your brain with daily training games anywhere you are</string>
    <string name="start_training">Start Training</string>

    <string name="multitasking_title">Multitasking Training</string>
    <string name="multitasking_description">In this multitasking experiment, we compare performance when just doing one task compared to when two tasks are mixed. </string>
    <string name="multitasking_use">
        Useful for:
        \n1. Carrying out multiple tasks at the same time like driving while talking on the phone
        \n2. Carrying out multiple tasks in rapid sequential order like cooking </string>
    <string name="multitasking_instructions">You will be shown these four figures in sequential trials
        \n1. When on the top "Shape" space, you will classify them by the shape ONLY.
        \n2. When on the bottom "Filling" space, you will classify them by the the number of dots ONLY.
        \n3. On the mix challenge you will have to switch classification depending if the figure is at the top or bottom
    </string>
    <string name="continue_to_instrucitons">Continue to Instructions</string>
    <string name="see_past_scores">See your progress on this task</string>

    <string name="choose">Choose your training task:</string>

    <string name="search_title">Visual Search Training</string>
    <string name="search_description"> Visual search is a type of perceptual task requiring attention that involves an active scan of the visual environment for a particular object among others</string>
    <string name="search_use">
         Useful for:
        \n1. Looking for your keys on the table before you leave
        \n2.Finding a friend in a large crowd of people
    </string>
    <string name="search_instr_title">Search Instructions</string>
    <string name="search_instr_desc">
        The goal of the game is to find the orange T as fast as possible.
        There will be blue Ts and upside down orange Ts to distract you.
        If there is an orange T, click "Found it"
        If there is no orange T, click "No Orange T"
    </string>
    <string name="search_instr_train">Train</string>
    <string name="search_instr_play">Play</string>
    <string name="search_found">Found It</string>
    <string name="search_not_found">No Orange T</string>
    <string name="play">Start Playing</string>

    <string name="results_avg_time">Average Response Time:</string>
    <string name="results_score">Total Score:</string>

    <string name="memory_title">Memory Training</string>
    <string name="memory_description">Concentration is a type of visuo-spatial memory task that involves recalling and manipulating images to keep track of the location of moving objects</string>
    <string name="memory_use">
         Useful for:
        \n1.Recalling where you saw things last in your apartment
        \n2.Better letter/number recognition when reading or performing arithmetic tasks
    </string>
    <string name="memory_instructions">
        1.Click on the cards to reveal the icon
        \n2.Remember the position and icon of the card you saw
        \n3.Try to pair two cards with the same icon together to earn points
    </string>
</resources>